chroniclesofelyria.com 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy - Chronicles of Elyria

Last Updated: March 2015

Soulbound Studios, LLC believes strongly that protecting our customers' privacy and security is a top priority. The following privacy policy describes what types of information we gather about you and what we will and will not do with it. 

### Collection of Information

We may collect personally identifiable information like names, addresses, email addresses, etc... when voluntarily submitted by you to place an order, ask a question, or sign up for a newsletter. The information you provide is only used to fulfill your specific request. Your personal information will not be shared with third parties or sold at any time. 

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookies and tracking technology to improve our services and web site. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. We will not share your personal information with third parties for the purpose of marketing, nor will we ever sell your information. 

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us by emailing [privacy@soulboundstudios.com](mailto:privacy@soulboundstudios.com)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
